* *
Okay, Danica, spill the beans.
Where are we going for
my bachelorette party, hmm?
Burlesque seafood buffet
in Reno?
The theme was going to be
"Trapped in a Mine."
You know, because
marriage is a trap.
But Carly vetoed my idea
without so much as
a petite rendezvous.
We are going to...
Ohio!
I said...
We heard you.
Wait. Are we gonna be
on my favorite TV show
Toledo House Flip?
No.
But we are going to the
"Party Like They Do
on Toledo House Flip
Experience."
You know how gals go to New York
to do the Sex and the City
tours?
So, it's gonna be exactly like
that, except we're going to be
"remodeling" a house
in the Midwest.
We're gonna have so much fun.
Placing succulents in corners,
and choosing between zebra
and giraffe wallpaper.
And screwing in Edison light
bulbs while drinking mimosas.
So you changed the entire
weekend on a whim?
Classic Carly.
Don't worry. I approved Carly's
itinerary, which means a lot
because I'm the queen
of bachelorette parties.
You've been
a maid of honor before?
14 times. All featured in
Bachelorette Party magazine.
Self-published.
Hey. Did you tell her?
Did you tell her?
Did she freak out?
Did she... flip?
Yoo-hoo, Freddie, a word?
Hey, um, question.
When you hear
"Classic Carly"...
Oh, no. My mom said
"Classic Carly"?
Why, what does it mean?
My mom kind of thinks
that you're...
impulsive, unreliable,
disrespectful to elders,
and prone to
hijacking a weekend.
Is that all?
No. She also thinks
you have poor posture.
But that's all.
I am going to prove
to her this weekend
that I am respectful, reliable,
and that I can
stand up straight.
God, my spine burns.
Don't worry, okay?
She's gonna love it.
Have fun. I love you.
And I love you, Millicent.
-Millicent?
-Bye.
Fredward, I just--
Bye, Danica.
-Take care, Harps.
-Oh.
And now a goodbye to the one
I'm going to miss the most...
Ooh.
Carly.
Sorry, what did you want
to tell me, Mom?
I don't recall.
Then it must not have
been important.
See ya, Mama. Hang loose.
Hang looser.
Classic Carly.
* I know *
* You see *
* Somehow the world
will change for me *
* And be so wonderful *
* So wake up
the members of my nation *
* It's your time to be *
* There's no chance
unless you take one *
* And the time to see
the brighter side *
* Of every situation *
* Some things are meant to be *
* So give your best
and leave the rest to me. *
* *
How fun is flying Southwest?
You never know where
you're gonna sit.
And yet somehow I ended up
next to you.
Is this a murder house?
There was never a conviction.
Hi. So, the brochure made
it seem less, um, meth-y?
And I'm very dependable,
so I wouldn't have
booked something meth-y.
You're saying meth a lot.
Let me see your teeth.
Welcome, ladies.
I'm Emily Haines,
and I'm honored you booked
the "Party Like They Do on
Toledo House Flip Experience."
Rehabbing a home
is good for the soul.
Talk to Carly about rehab,
she's the one who's
babbling on about meth.
This is the bride, Marissa.
I'm the maid of honor.
One would think I
would've been the one
to pick what we're
doing this weekend,
but one would be wrong.
Now, I just need one member
of the group
to sign here
so we can get started.
I know it's called "Party Like
They Do on Toledo House Flip,"
but it's strange
because it seems like
we're about to be
doing actual labor?
Relax, it's all part
of the experience.
Plus, you get to wear jumpsuits!
Oh, good.
Manual labor and you're making
it harder for me to pee.
Never underestimate the power
of women in pink jumpsuits.
Amen.
Now, hand over your phones.
When we unplug from the world,
we plug in with each other.
Ooh, plug language.
I definitely want to plug in
with y'all.
So, hand them over, ladies.
Where we're going,
we don't need phones.
It's weird. For someone
so claustrophobic,
you sure do enjoy invading
others' personal space.
* *
Well, I guess it is a Saturday.
Oh!
-Aah!
-Lewbert.
What the hell are you doing?
Well, Marissa said you'd
throw me a bachelor party.
Didn't she tell you?
I think she tried to.
What's in the growler?
Oh, a family recipe:
Lewb Juice.
It's a delicious libation
and a darn strong
foot exfoliant.
Shall I pour?
That's gross and I don't want
to do this
and I'm mad at my mom now.
Okay. You know,
Marissa said your
unreliable girlfriend
would rub off on you.
Classic Carly.
Wait. Fine.
I'll give you a party.
Who do you want me to invite?
Hello?
Hey, man, you busy?
No, what's up?
Apparently,
my mom promised Lewbert
I would throw him
a bachelor party tonight.
Oh, hey, hey, can I invite Paul?
He seems like somebody I can
pretend to like IPAs with.
Yeah, sure, he's an additional
human male.
In five, four, three...
* This is The Paul Show,
and I am Paul *
Damn it, when is it my turn?
You've got Paul, manager,
impresario, size 15 shoe.
Oh, yeah, we're gonna
be friends.
Oh, hey, what's up, man?
It's Spencer Shay.
Uh, yeah, I was just wondering,
uh, you into bachelor parties?
Oh, I'm not into
bachelor parties.
I'm the king of
How soon can you be
in my apartment?
Oh, an hour. I-I'm upstairs
but I got to go home
and get my poppers.
Zut alors.
I didn't realize
this would be so physical.
It's not so bad.
Normally, people pay $50
to do hungover Pilates.
This is just like that,
only with more tetanus.
If I get tetanus,
can I sit down?
You know what?
Let's play a game.
And the name of the game
that I'm about to say is...
"Truth or Hammer!"
Oh, yes. The famous party
game that everyone knows.
Truth or Hammer is
a very real game that exists...
where we go around and ask each
other penetrating questions.
And if anyone doesn't
want to answer,
then it's hammer time.
Wow, that actually kind of
made sense.
And as
Bachelorette Party Tsarina,
I brought Mrs. B's
favorite libation. Grenadine!
Shots! Shots!
Non-alcoholic shots!
Wow, is this party
iconic or what?
Danica, have you ever flirted
with a man you knew was taken?
Oui oui. But the French
never kiss and tell.
You're from Idaho.
I guess it's hammer time.
Okay. Harper!
Who is your best kiss?
Ooh, you want me to choose
between 100-- lies-- 300 people?
It's hammer time!
Okay, Carly's turn.
What's the most romantic place
you've been with Freddie?
Ooh.
Oh. I know where
it's going to be.
Freddie's taking me
on a two-day cruise...
...to Jamaica...
...on the second Sunday in May.
Mother's Day weekend?!
Why wasn't I invited?
Because that would be weird.
Oh, no. Not weird.
No, that's so normal.
Come with, girlfriend.
We can even set up a cot
in the cabin.
That I will be sleeping on.
Marissa, let's put
down the hammer.
You're not storming
the Bastille.
I want to go home.
Well, you tried, Carly.
Poorly, but you tried.
Ah, stay the course.
This is a part
of every bachelorette party:
the bride must cry
for no rhyme or reason.
You're doing great, sweetie.
Screw this party.
I just wanted Mrs. B to like me.
Ladies, let's go.
Oh, hey, girl.
Where do you think you're going?
You're trapped.
-Trapped?
-Perhaps I was being
a dot dramatic.
You can leave anytime.
Once the house is flipped.
It's all explained here.
That waiver? But none of us
signed it except Carly.
She signed for your entire
group unilaterally.
-Classic Carly.
So now I'm what?
Someone who signs waivers
on behalf of a group?
Yup.
It's not a waiver.
It's an employment contract.
And that HGTV B-I-T-C-H
has our phones.
I say we smash that case.
Go ahead.
My fiancé made this lockbox,
and he designed the deathtraps
for the movie Saw.
Ladies, you're just
contracted construction workers
until the home is done.
Simple pimple.
This contract doesn't include
a minor's permit.
I'm well-versed
in Ohio's child labor laws.
Guess that makes you
my co-captain.
You up for delineating tasks
while drinking cold
sparkling apple cider?
Keep the meaningless title.
I accept the power
and the juice.
How long will this take?
I left my mouse Julien with
a bowl of food and a note.
That mouse is dead.
I had a party flip a house
in two days.
Well, a 500-square-foot studio.
Never underestimate the power
of women in pink jumpsuits.
Don't worry, we've got this.
Because we, including me,
are dependable, decisive,
straight-spined gals.
Oh, has anyone been up
to the second floor?
There's a second floor?
Oh, I can't believe you went
to all this trouble for me.
Well, a boy's best friend
is his mother.
By the way,
have you heard from her?
Oh, not a peep.
Although, sometimes Marissa
pretends to go missing.
It's sort of an elaborate
psychosexual prank. You see--
Now! For the love of God, now!
* *
Lock the doors
and lower the blinds!
It's bachelor party time!
Oh, it's happening!
I'm the bachie!
Bachie! Bachie! Bachie!
All my friends are here!
Best bachelor party ever!
So...
what's next?
Next?
This is the thing.
Or...
Lewb Juice?
So, it's a drink
and a foot exfoliant?
You know, I thought Lewb Juice
would taste terrible
because the name,
like Lewbert, is disgusting.
-Lewbert is disgusting.
-Yeah.
You are disgusting.
Does Lewb Juice make you mean?
No, it just makes you honest.
Dissolves the skin off your feet
and the filter off your brain.
Go ahead, try to lie.
I like Ben Affleck's back
tattoo. I think it's hip.
That's incredible.
I wish you weren't
marrying my mother.
I wish you weren't her son.
Sometimes I wonder how far
I can take this lovable
goofball thing.
Will I ever have to grow up?
If I did, I'd want
to be like you.
Please, you're the cool one,
Captain Charisma.
Oh.
Oh, my God, no.
Is it that bitch Trina
from poison control?
She said I could
still drink Lewb Juice
as long as I didn't sell it!
Guys, this is an emergency.
We got to go.
-Oh, God!
-My feet!
-It burns!
I have friends.
Carly, you really know how
to plan a bachelorette party.
Danica, when you're done with
the wall, paint my nails.
Hey, hey.
At least the hard hats are pink.
Okay, ladies, quick vibe check.
The vibe? It's giving "hostage."
Then it's time for Stockholm
Syndrome because I'm thinking
Scandinavian modern
for these floors.
Then we need to go over
a long list of other changes.
Ugh, changes? Why can't things
just stay the same?
Same house, same walls,
same little boy who kisses me
on the cheek before anyone else
when saying goodbye!
Oh, this is about Freddie.
Who's Freddie again?
It's Carly's boyfriend
and Millicent's dad.
He was my son first!
-Mrs. B, wait!
-No, no.
This is a part of it.
Phase one, shots. Phase two,
the bride wants to leave.
Phase three, the coolest person
at the party
calms everyone down.
That's what's currently
happening.
Screw you, ladies!
Mrs. Benson, where are you?
You're kind of freaking us out.
I'm in the walls, suckas!
This is not a known phase.
I can't sell this house
with a woman in the wall.
That's a $20,000 markdown.
Wait, I thought you were
an event planner.
You're also the realtor?
Damn, girl, you got
capitalism figured out.
If any of you ever
want to leave,
you better get her out of there.
Now it looks like we're
talking to something
and not an actual wall.
Mrs. B, I know you can hear me.
I can't hear you, Carly.
We have to get you out of there.
Leave me be.
This is my safe space.
Do most safe spaces
have asbestos?
-Hey.
-We're here!
You came to rescue us?
Yes, we did.
Like four gallant kni-aah!
What in God's name is happening?
We've been drinking Lewb Juice.
It's a foot exfoliant,
which is why we can't walk.
It's also a truth serum,
which is why I want one of those
jumpsuits in an XL
so I can feel like I belong.
Oh!
Where's my mom?
Funny story, actually.
Um, your mother hates me
and this weekend so much
that she is... in the walls.
Classic Mommy.
All right, I'll get her out.
I can't do this.
Well, then I have no choice.
Mrs. Benson, I'm coming for you!
You can depend on me!
I can hear you slouching.
Oh, the crawlspace.
Carly, your claustrophobia.
Grease up my shoulders,
I am going in.
Come to Toledo, get together,
flip a house,
have a few laughs...
Bruce Willis,
you damn national treasure,
how the hell did you
make it look so easy?
Aah!
Oh, yippee-ki-yay,
Freddie's mother.
Thank God you're okay!
Oh, look. I went into
my safe space,
and you ran in and took over.
Classic Carly.
Enough.
We both love Freddie so much.
We should be on the same team.
Freddie and I were a team.
But ever since you showed up,
it's like he put me
on the bench.
I hate sports.
I never really looked
at it that way.
Carly, that's so loud.
Marissa! I will get you
out of there!
I see a saw.
Could someone saw off my feet?!
How did you guys find us?
I texted Dad.
When Emily wasn't looking,
I took a crack at her lockbox.
The code was 1234.
Simple pimple indeed.
Wait, you got to our phones?
I could've called Julien
and told him how to get
a bottle of water.
Don't challenge my methods.
I'm the hero.
I'm the real hero!
I bet you hate me now
more than ever.
I don't hate you, Carly.
I just hate change, especially
when it comes to Freddie.
Also, I truly hate your posture.
But I can't believe you crawled
into the wall for me.
Both because of
your claustrophobia
and your obvious
character flaws.
Of course I did.
I love Team Benson.
And I'm always going to
be your biggest cheerleader.
And maybe someday,
I'll be a Benson, too.
-Mm.
-Sorry.
Yeah, I-I shouldn't
have said that.
Could you just keep
that between us?
What happens in the wall
stays in the wall.
But if you think he's marrying
Little Miss Scoliosis,
you've had a bit
too much grenadine.
Yeah, let's get out of here.
I think we've had enough truth.
How about some hammer?
Here's Mommy!
Hey!
Your girlfriend faced her
worst fears to rescue me.
Classic Carly.
Oh, my favorite girls,
get in here.
Carly, Mom, Millicent!
I'm a'ight.
Well, ladies,
this house looks even worse
than when you started.
I'm glad you found
a passel of men to help,
because at the pace
you're going,
you'll be in Ohio for months
to fulfill the terms
of your contract.
I'd like to talk about
your little...
employment contract.
Oh, snap, it's his lawyer voice.
I perused your contract
and it fails to address
the fact that Ohio
is an at-will employment state.
-But they signed--
-Which means...
an employee may quit their job
at any time for any reason.
Regardless of a contact.
Tell her, Pop Pop.
So, unless you'd like to face
charges of kidnapping, fraud,
then I suggest you refund
these ladies' money
and never speak of this again.
Yeah!
The bride cried, we took shots--
I came to rescue you
and you rescued my mom.
Bruce Willis could never.
Mm.
Ooh, and someone made out.
With their boyfriend.
Still counts. We did it, Joe.
Ooh!
* *
-* Y'all ready for this *
-Oh, my God!
* *
* This is The Paul Show
and I am Paul *
Welcome back to Paul or Nothing.
Today, respected doorman-
turned-lawyer Lewbert Sline
is gonna show us how to
make his famous Lewb Juice.
Step one. Warm cough syrup,
boiled in the mouth
of an active volcano.
Step two. Some nice,
expired nut milk.
And I don't mean almonds.
That's my man.
You're welcome, Internet.
* *
Ooh!